Bob Bullock Campaigns papers, Inclusive: 1970-1996, Bulk: 1973-1996
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- 1990 Campaign, 1973-1991; 5
  - Issues, 1979-1991; 14
    - Labor, 1979-1991; 7
      - Press Releases, 1989 October (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Press Releases, 1990 December (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Directories, 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Publications: Directories, 1990 July-September (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Publications: Directories, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Publications: General, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Reports, 1991 January (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Other, 1988-1990; 8
      - 1990 Census, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Affirmative Action, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Airplanes, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - American Ethnic Coalition, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Asian Community in Texas, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Audits, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Bureaucratic Waste, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Campaign Contributions, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - Conflict of Interest, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - Coryell County District Judge, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - Daylight Savings Time, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - Democratic Party, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 23)
      - Economic Development, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 24)
      - Education, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 25)
      - Emission Control, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 26)
      - Entrenched Bureaucracy, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - Ethics and International Business, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 28)
      - Family Values, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 29)
      - FBI, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 30)
      - Fiscal Notes, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 31)
      - Franchise Tax, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 32)
      - Galveston Track, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 33)
      - General, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 34)
      - Gramm, Phil, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 35)
      - Greenberg, Fisk, Bush & Walker, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 36)
      - Impact of Proposed Defense Cuts, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 37)
      - Industry-Mailing List, circa 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 38)
      - Insurance Lobby, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 39)
      - KHOU-Houston, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Land Lease, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Lottery, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Mail Order Bill, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Male Rights Advocacy, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Mandatory Helmet Law, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - MHMR, 1989-990 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - “Mud Slinging”, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - National Convention Ratification, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - National Rifle Association, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - News Clippings, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - News Clippings, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - News Clippings, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Park Proposals, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Prayer In Public Schools, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Prisons, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Publications, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Responsible Use of Animals, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Sales Tax, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - S.E.R. Programs, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Soft Money Contributions, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Smoking, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - State Agencies, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - State Job Training, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - Student Requests, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - Texas Eagle Forum, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - Texas State Artist, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 27)
      - Texas Economy, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - Toxic Waste Disposal, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 29)
      - United Airlines, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 30)
      - Urban Development, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Itineraries, 1990-1991; 15
    - Calendars, 1990 January (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Calendars, 1990 February (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Calendars, 1990 March (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Calendars, 1990 April (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Calendars, 1990 May (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Calendars, 1990 June (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Calendars, 1990 July (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Calendars, 1990 August (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Calendars, 1990 September (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Calendars, 1990 October (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Calendars, 1990 November (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Calendars, 1990 December (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Calendars, 1991 January (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Schedules, 1990 January (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Schedules, 1990 February (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Schedules, 1990 March (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Schedules, 1990 April (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Schedules, 1990 May (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Schedules, 1990 June 4-August 22 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Schedules, 1990 July 30-August 31 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Schedules, 1990 August 7-August 30 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Schedules, 1990 August 22-September 17 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Schedules, 1990 October 1-November 22 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Schedules, 1990 December (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Jan Bullock, 1990 March (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Jan Bullock, 1990 April (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Jan Bullock, 1990 May (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Jan Bullock, 1990 June (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Jan Bullock, 1990 July (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Jan Bullock, 1990 August (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Jan Bullock, 1990 September (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Jan Bullock, 1990 October (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Jan Bullock: Biographical Matl., circa 1990 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Jan Bullock: Form Letter & Release, circa 1990 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Jan Bullock: Trip Log, 1990 March-October (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Mosbacher, 1979-1990; 16
    Mosbacher includes fourteen sub-subseries: Advertising, Contribution and Expense Reports, Correspondence, Department of Human Services, Endorsements, Federal Election Commission, Financial, Interested Party Memos, Mail Outs, News clippings, Open Records, Press, Robert, Sr. and Georgette, and Notebooks.
    This subseries details Bullock’s Republican opposition Rob Mosbacher. It is a sizable subseries and shows Bullock’s dedication to his 1990 campaign for lieutenant governor. Bullock kept files on many aspects of his opponents’ campaigns, all found within the Mosbacher subseries.
    - Advertising, 1990; 1
      - Advertising, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Contribution and Expense Reports, 1979-1990; 2
      - General (1 of 2), 1989 August 3-December 31 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - General (2 of 2), 1989 August 3-December 31 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - General, 1990 January-June (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - General, 1990 July-September 27 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - General (1 of 2), 1990 September 28-October 27 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - General (2 of 2), 1990 September 28-October 27 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - General (1 of 2), 1990 October 28-December 31 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - General (2 of 2), 1990 October 28-December 31 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - General, 1991 January 1-June 30 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Expenditures and Payments, 1990 January-June (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Expenditures/Payments/Returned Contributions, 1990 July-September 27 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Special Purpose Committee, pg. 1-50, 1979 August 3-1989 December (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Special Purpose Committee, pg. 51-100, 1979 August 3-1989 December (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Special Purpose Committee, pg. 101-150, 1979 August 3-1989 December (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Special Purpose Committee, pg. 151-200, 1979 August 3-1989 December (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Special Purpose Committee, pg. 201-250, 1979 August 3-1989 December (Box 27, Folder 17)
      - Special Purpose Committee, pg. 251-303, 1979 August 3-1989 December (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Specific Purpose Committee, pg. 1-50, 1990 January-June (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Specific Purpose Committee, pg. 51-100, 1990 January-June (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Specific Purpose Committee, pg. 101-150, 1990 January-June (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Specific Purpose Committee, pg. 151-200, 1990 January-June (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Specific Purpose Committee, pg. 201-250, 1990 January-June (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Specific Purpose Committee, pg. 251-300, 1990 January-June (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Specific Purpose Committee, pg. 301-350, 1990 January-June (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Specific Purpose Committee, pg. 351-400, 1990 January-June (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Specific Purpose Committee, pg. 401-450, 1990 January-June (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Specific Purpose Committee, pg. 451-505, 1990 January-June (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Specific Purpose Committee, pg. 1-50, 1990 July-September 27 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Specific Purpose Committee, pg. 51-100, 1990 July-September 27 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Specific Purpose Committee, pg. 101-150, 1990 July-September 27 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Specific Purpose Committee, pg. 151-200, 1990 July-September 27 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Specific Purpose Committee, pg. 201-218, 1990 July-September 27 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - Specific Purpose Committee, Alphabetic List, pg. 1-50, 1990 July-September 27 (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - Specific Purpose Committee, Alphabetic List, pg. 51-100, 1990 July-September 27 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Specific Purpose Committee, Alphabetic List, pg. 101-150, 1990 July-September 27 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Specific Purpose Committee, Alphabetic List, pg. 151-200, 1990 July-September 27 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Specific Purpose Committee, Alphabetic List, pg. 201-261, 1990 July-September 27 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1990; 3
      - Bullock Supporters, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Bullock Supporters, 1990 February-July (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Bullock Supporters, 1990 August-December (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Department of Human Services, 1988 June 14, September 20 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Department of Human Services, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - General, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - General, 1989 January (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - General, 1989 February (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - General, 1989 April (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - General, 1989 June (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - General, 1989 July (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - General, 1989 September (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - General, 1989 November (Box 29, Folder 17)
      - General, 1990 January (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - General, 1990 February (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - General, 1990 March (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - General, 1990 April (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - General, 1990 May (Box 29, Folder 22)
      - General, 1990 June (Box 29, Folder 23)
      - General, 1990 July (Box 29, Folder 24)
      - General, 1990 August (Box 29, Folder 25)
      - General, 1990 September (Box 29, Folder 26)
      - General, 1990 October (Box 29, Folder 27)
      - General, circa 1990, undated (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Department of Human Services, 1990; 4
      - Bullock Special Briefing Book (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Bullock Special Briefing Book (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Endorsements, 1990; 5
      - Received, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Federal Election Commission, 1983-1984; 6
      - Candidate Index of Supporting Documents, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Financial, 1982-1990; 7
      - Duplicate Donations to Bullock & Mosbacher List, 1982-1990 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Hollywood Marine PAC, 1990 September-October (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Income Tax Return, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Income Tax Return (Amended), 1985 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Income Tax Return, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Income Tax Return, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Income Tax Return (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Income Tax Return (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Interested Parties Memos, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Interested Parties Memos, 1990 February-June (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Interested Parties Memos, 1990 July-September (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Interested Parties Memos, 1990 October-November (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Political Action Committee (PAC) Information, 1990 July (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - Political Action Committee (PAC) Information, 1990 August (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - Tax Return Notes, 1984-1988 (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - U.S. Senate Campaign Finances, 1983 June-1984 December (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - Washington Insider Contributions, undated (Box 30, Folder 21)
      - Fundraisers, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 22)
      - Fundraisers, 1990 January-August (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Fundraisers, 1990 October (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Interested Party Memos, 1988-1990; 8
      - Barges/Environment (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Barges/Environment (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Department of Human Services, 1990 January (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Department of Human Services, 1990 February (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Department of Human Services, 1990 March (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Department of Human Services, 1990 April-May (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Department of Human Services, 1990 June-September (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - General, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - General, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Income Taxes/Personal Finance, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Income Taxes/Personal Finance, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Issues, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Issues, 1990 January (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - Issues, 1990 February (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Issues, 1990 March-April (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - Issues, 1990 July-October (Box 31, Folder 18)
      - Issues, undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Mail Outs, 1989-1990; 9
      - Mail Outs, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Mail Outs (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Mail Outs (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - News Clippings, 1989-1990; 10
      - News Clippings, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - News Clippings, 1990 January-February (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - News Clippings, 1990 March-April (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - News Clippings, 1990 May-November (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Newspaper Booklet, circa 1990 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Open Records, 1989-1990; 11
      - Open Records Requested of Bullock, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Requests, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Requests, 1990 January (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Requests, 1990 February (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Requests, 1990 March (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Requests, 1990 April (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Requests, 1990 May (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Requests, 1990 June (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Requests, 1990 July (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Requests, 1990 August (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Requests, 1990 September (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - Requests, 1990 October (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - Requests, 1990 November (Box 32, Folder 21)
      - Requests 1990 List Through August 14 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Press, 1989-1990; 12
      - Press Kit, circa 1990 (Box 32, Folder 23)
      - Press Releases, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - Press Releases, 1990 January-March (Box 32, Folder 25)
      - Press Releases, 1990 July-August (Box 32, Folder 26)
      - Press Releases, 1990 September-December (Box 32, Folder 27)
      - Press Releases, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Robert, Sr. and Georgette, 1988-1990; 13
      - General, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - General, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - General, 1990, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Publication: The Washington Post Article, 1989 January 15 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Notebooks, 1989-1990; 14
      - 1990 Campaign Notebook, 1989-1990 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - 1990 Endorsements Notebook, 1990 September-November (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Race for Lieutenant Governor, Vol. 1 & 2, 1989-1990 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Polls, 1987-1991; 17
    - 5th Senatorial District Poll-Emory & Young, 1990 August 14 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - 1990 Statewide Elections/Public Perception of Major Issues-The Texas Poll, 1990 April-May (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - AMA Party Issues Survey, No.6-Hamilton, Frederick & Schneiders, 1988 June (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Articles, 1987 October (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Articles, 1989 March (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Articles, 1990 March (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Articles, 1990 April (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Articles, 1990 May (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Articles, 1990 September (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Articles, 1990 October (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Associated General Contractors Poll-Dick Murray, 1988 July (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Ector County Public Opinion Survey-Rick Knox & Associates, 1989 September-October (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Chet Edwards Benchmark Assessment Survey-Cooper & Secrest Associates, 1989 July (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Eppstein Polls-General Information, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Focus Group Findings-Democratic Primary 1990, Sibley & Associates, 1990 September 8 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Gallup Poll Survey of Public Opinion in Texas on Ethics-Texas Public Policy FDN., circa 1989-1990 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - General Election Survey Results-The Eppstein Group, Summary, 1990 September 6 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - General Election Survey Results-The Eppstein Group, Tabulations, Questions 1 & 2 Plus Intro, 1990 September 6 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - General Election Survey Results-The Eppstein Group, Tabulations, Questions 3 & 4, 1990 September 6 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - General Election Survey Results-The Eppstein Group, Tabulations, Questions 5-23, 1990 September 6 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - General Election Benchmark Survey of Public Attitudes-Texas Lieutenant Governor, Shipley & Associates, 1990 May-June (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - General Information, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - General Information, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - General Information, 1990 February (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - General Information, 1990 March-August (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - General Information-Shipley Polls, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Hamilton Polls, 1988-1989 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Informal Polling-Mosbacher Media Testing, Public Strategies, 1990 July 12 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - J.J. Pickle Polls, 1990 August-October (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - John Bryant Campaign-5th District Survey, 1990 October (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Lists-General, 1987-1990 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Mason Dixon Survey Report, 1988 June (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Mason Dixon Survey Report, 1990 August (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - McLennan County Democratic Party Stray Poll, 1989 March 30 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Mike Moncrief-Senate #12 Benchmark Poll, circa 1989-1990 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - National Message/Theme Poll, 1989 December 6 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Phone Bank Polls, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Phone Bank Polls, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Polling Results Charts, 1990 October (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Pre-Labor Day Poll-Lieutenant Governor, Shipley & Associates, 1990 September (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Preliminary Poll Results, 1989 June 14 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Press Release, 1989 September (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Public Affairs Opinion Survey-John Ben Shepperd Leadership Forum, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Richards Polls, 1989 August (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Special Report from The Texas Poll, 1990 Spring (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Statewide Survey on Abortion-Texas Abortion Rights Action League, 1990 March (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Survey of Public Attitudes in the State of Texas, 1989 December (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Survey of Public Attitudes-Shipley & Associates, 1987 October (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Survey of Public Attitudes-Shipley & Associates, 1988 June (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Survey of Public Attitudes-Shipley & Associates, 1989 May-June (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Survey of Public Opinion in Texas on Ethics-Texas Public Policy Foundation, 1991 January (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Texas Chamber Poll, 1990 March (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Texas Electric Co-Op Association Straw Poll, 1990 August 10 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Texas Interested Citizens General Tracking Survey, Vol. 1 & 2-The Eppstein Group, 1990 October (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Texas Health Profile-Texas Department of Health, 1990 May (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - The Texas Poll, pgs. TOC, 1-4, 109-157, 254-301, 1989 August 5 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - The Texas Poll, pgs. 1404-1448, 1539-1582, 1989 July 22-August 5 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - The Texas Poll, pgs. TOC-52, 1990 January 27-February 8 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - The Texas Poll, pgs. 137-206, 307-324, 359-400, 1990 January 27-February 8 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - The Texas Poll, pgs. 401-500, 1990 January 27-February 8 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - The Texas Poll, pgs. 501-600, 1990 January 27-February 8 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - The Texas Poll, pgs. 601-700, 1990 January 27-February 8 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - The Texas Poll, pgs. 701-766, 1990 January 27-February 8 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - The Texas Poll Report, 1988 Spring (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - The Texas Poll Report, 1989 Spring (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - The Texas Poll Report, 1989 Fall (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - The Texas Poll Report, 1990 Spring (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - The Texas Poll Report, 1990 October (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - The Texas Poll Report, 1990 Winter (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Position Papers, 1988-1990; 18
    - The Texas Poll, Survey II & III-The Gallup Organization, 1990 October (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Texas Senate District 9-Shipley & Associates, 1990 December (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Texas Statewide Survey-Shipley & Associates, 1988 September 1 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Texas Statewide Survey, Survey Crosstabulations-Houston/Dallas, 1990 June 11 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Texas Unity ’90 Campaign, Tabular Report-Hickman Maslin, 1990 August (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - TEXPAC Poll-Democratic Primary Voters-Survey of Public Attitudes, Shipley & Associates, 1989 December (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Tracking, Shipley & Associates, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - University of Texas at Dallas Texas Legislative Survey, 1990 May (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Wilson Campaign, Shipley & Associates, 1990 September 17 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Zaffirini Poll, 1990 August 14 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Budget Plan, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Crime and Drugs, circa 1990 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Environment, circa 1990 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Health Care, circa 1990 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Higher Education, circa 1990 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Jobs for Texans, circa 1990 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Making Texas Government Work, circa 1990 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - “New Start” Budget for Texas, circa 1990 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Public Education, circa 1990 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Tax Equity, circa 1990 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Publications, 1987-1990; 19
    The Publications subseries has six sub-subseries: Articles, Brochures, Debates, News clippings, Newsletters, and Press Releases. Publicity covers various forms of public media which Bullock collected or people sent him about himself, his campaigns, and politics in general. The various forms of publications are arranged chronologically and contain information about the political climate and events surrounding Bullock’s political campaigns.
    - Articles, 1987-1990; 1
      - General, 1987 February (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - General, 1988 April (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - General, 1990 October (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Brochures, 1989-1990; 2
      - The Bullock Education Plan, circa 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Mosbacher Brochures-Negative, circa 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Debates, 1990; 3
      - Decision ’90, KERA Channel 13, 1990 August-October (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - News clippings, 1987-1990; 4
      - General, 1987 January (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - General, 1987 September (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - General, 1987 October (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - General, 1987 November (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - General, 1988 January (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - General, 1990 March (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - General, 1990 May (Box 36, Folder 13)